lacf.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online by Fairplex. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

**Notice**

Fairplex uses personal information to better understand your needs and interest and provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your relationship with Fairplex. Fairplex will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others.

This privacy statement covers personally identifiable information, anonymous data collection and aggregate reporting. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name or personal identity. Anonymous (non-personal) information is data about usage and service operation, reported in aggregate, which is not associated to a specific personal identity. Aggregate information is data collected and summarized for a broad category. 

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When submitting a form through our website, the information that you provide to the Fairplex may include any of the following (“Contact Information”): 

  * Name
  * E-Mail Address
  * Telephone Number
  * Mailing Address

Fairplex does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18 and Fairplex is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents to take an active role in your child's online activities and interests. 

**When do we collect information?**

Anonymous (non-personal) data we collect may include the pages visited on fairplex.com, lacountyfair.com and mobile apps including unique URLs visited within Fairplex properties, browser type and IP address. Most anonymous data is collected via cookies, session variables, log files or other analysis technologies.

We may also collect personal information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

Fairplex will not sell or rent your personally identifiable Contact Information to anyone. However, Fairplex may share such information with other companies or people when: 

  * We have your permission to share this information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the event, directions, products, information, or services you have requested; or
  * We have a third-parties assist us in providing materials and information about upcoming events sponsored or produced by Fairplex.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Fairplex reserves the right to modify or amend this policy at any time by posting the revised privacy policy on our site. The changes will only affect the information we collect after the effective date of the change to our privacy policy unless we clearly express otherwise. 

**Contacting us**

We value your comments and opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send your request by e-mail to [webmaster@fairplex.com](mailto:webmaster@fairplex.com).
